This New Year's Eve, the countdown to love is on.
Midnight at the Magnolia is a romance, comedy, tv
movie film directed by Max McGuire.
Longtime friends and local radio hosts Maggie and Jack fake it as a couple for their
families and listeners in hopes of getting their show syndicated.
Maggie Quinn, played by Natalie Hall.
Jack Russo, played by Evan Williams.
Deb Clarkson, played by Alison Brooks.
Steve Quinn, played by Steve Cumyn.
Martin Russo, played by Michael Gordin Shore.
Amanda, played by Victoria Maria.
Magnolia Pictures LLC is an American independent film distributor and production company,
and is a subsidiary of Mark Cuban and Todd Wagner's 2929 Entertainment.
Magnolia was formed in 2001 by Bill Banowsky and Eamonn Bowles, and
specializes in both foreign and independent films.
Magnolia distributes some of its films, especially foreign and
genre titles, under the Magnet Releasing arm.
In April 2011, Cuban had placed Magnolia up for sale, but stated that he would not sell the company unless the offer was "very,
very compelling."
Magnify, formerly Magnolia Pictures International, is the global sales arm of Magnolia Pictures.
The film explores themes of new year's eve, holiday,
lying, friends in love, radio host.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.